Michael Catapang

Metro Manila

catapangmichaelsuarez@gmail.com

09760383469

linkedin.com/in/mikecatapang

Summary

A Qualified IT Professional with 7 years of experience, including 3+ years of experience as a Service-Now suite developer and administrator. Experience in Configuring Applications using Service-Now tool, used in ITIL Management. Strong understanding of ITIL V3. Deep functional and technical knowledge of the Service Now platform as well as experience delivering medium to large-scale Service Now implementations.

Experience



ServiceNow Developer

Seven Seven

Dec 2020 - Present (3 years 4 months)

ServiceNow Developer/Administrator

Seven Seven

Dec 2020 - Oct 2023 (2 years 11 months)

DEPLOYED AT BANCO DE ORO

- Develop ITSM Module
- Configure and maintain SLA, catalog items and their associated workflows;
- Maintain the integrity of the ServiceNow platform across production and non-production instances.
- Collaborate with other administrators to develop solutions and changes
- Create Flow for catalog items using flow designer
- Create Client Script for some configurations and aesthetic of forms and list view
- Upgrade Patches monthly on mid server and review all the affected modules in platform and portal
- Working closely with IT and business partners to configure and improve core platform capabilities in accordance with ITIL best practices.
- Provide administration, development, maintenance, and technical support by using good practice to configure robust solutions to the BDO customer utilizing the ServiceNow platform.
- Manages and maintains relationships with key departments throughout the University to understand business needs, implement solutions and support customers.
- Vendor management and communication for escalation of critical issues and support of new system implementation and determination of root cause analysis.
- Conducts / participates in user inclusive story / requirement gathering sessions
- Update and maintain a comprehensive testing protocol for ServiceNow instance upgrades with the purpose of certifying all applications for use after the upgrade completes.
- ATF Testing coordination with Business analyst and normalize test script.
- Conduct Brown bag on service now and other modules to provide a knowledge transfer to the team.
- Attend Daily Stand up/meetings with other teams and vendor to give updates
- Develop enhancements and fix defects in ServiceNow
- Use Agile and SAFE for methodologies of the project

- Build and develop Virtual Agent for transition of their automated assistant on service portal and teams application

©, pricelocq

Supervisor Full stack Developer

LOCQ, INC.

May 2020 - Nov 2020 (7 months)

As the full stack developer, my core activities included:

Creating new features, functionality and capabilities on web application portals using react js + redux-thunk/saga and JSON.

Recommending Solution for a user friendly interface with the UX design team.

Performing bug fixes and code reviews.

Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.

Collaborate with technical manager and other developers.

Building stable and maintainable codebases using react

Creating reusable components for Global User interface

Work and assist agile transition process and collaborating with product owners and scrum master.

Create feature for event driven design using AWS and postgre sql.

Application Development Analyst- Software Engineer

Accenture

Aug 2018 - Mar 2020 (1 year 8 months)

Accomplishment:

Designed a code using Node JS for back-end, amazon web services for server including

DynamoDB, lambda function, RESTAPI'S, Angular 4 for front-end and JSON

I did support and hand-off with the operations team in Accenture India

I fixed mostly in front-end and gave enhancement to the user experience

Collaborate with product owners and planned for new requirements using Team foundation system own

by Microsoft integrated in Azure including co-developers and solution architect

Provide feedback every retrospective to improve the process of Scrum team

I Helped build and support for bugs and issue to fix immediate within the sprint

Unit testing for every component and function that need to be test before deploying on stage using jasmine framework

Demo with the stakeholder and clients for successful function every 2 weeks of the sprint

UI/UX Designer

Accenture

Aug 2018 - Mar 2020 (1 year 8 months)

Project I handled TEDO- Time and expense digital operations. TEDO is a internal chat bot of accenture that giving information of the employees of accenture nation wide. TEDO is inter-connected to web application which is (Metric Analytics platform). I coordinate with Product owners and stakeholders to give a best solution for new features and redesign function of TEDO including response of BOT. I also help the Engineers to implement and give them a high velocity of work to have a minimal implementation to UI such as giving Design system, CSS and HTML.

The same also on (Metric Analytics Platform): this web application is a monitoring system to monitor every internal agent of accenture and chat bots. I designed some function of the application and continuously working and serve a best solution to the client. what I did there I applied the design process every requirments that needed to implement like journey maps getting personas, user research and other process to implement the required design of the system.



Frontend Developer

New Oriental Club88 Corporation

Jan 2018 - Jul 2018 (7 months)

I code in back end and front-end as a junior developer in new oriental club88 and I'll be doing testing and debugging and fix the bugs and assist the senior developer to enhance modules and optimizations of the project. Collaboration for architecture and sphering for better development.

Freelance Project Manager

Ditel systems Inc.

Oct 2017 - Dec 2017 (3 months)

We provide a website to promote their business and advertise their products to social media. Me and other developer support the website and configured all emails for their formality in their clients. Included the hosting, outlook and maintaining the site.

Web Developer

Actionlab I.T services

Jun 2017 - Sep 2017 (4 months)

I assist the developers and do the task that was given and invovle in collaborations of architecture and optimizing the project.

Web developer intern

Long asia holdings inc

Mar 2016 - Nov 2016 (9 months)

- Graphic Designer of the system (Time Management System, PHP, CSS, JAVASCRIPT)
- · Network Trainee On site
- Create static website for the company
- Network Administrator (IT SUPPORT & TECHNICALS)

Education

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2013 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications

🙃 Angular & Node js - Mean Stack Guide - Udemy

Scrum Fundamentals Certified (SFC) - SCRUMstudy - Accreditation Body for Scrum and Agile



Skills

Technical Documentation • WordPress • Elementor • HTML • Business Rules • Test Planning • Troubleshooting • Skill Development • User Stories • Technical Support

Honors & Awards



Best in On The Job Trainee - Global Reciprocal Colleges

May 2017

I've been selected as one of our batch as best on the job trainee because of the grade and evaluation that I received from 2 companies I previously worked. I created payroll system, I set up their servers and created a website for their company.